<resources>
    <string name="app_name">provinceDisplay</string>
    <string name="btnNwt">Northwest Territories</string>
    <string name="btnNs">Nova Scotia</string>
    <string name="btnPei">Prince Edward Island</string>

    <string name="nwt_disp">
        Northwest Territories, region of northern and northwestern
        Canada encompassing a vast area of forests and tundra. The
        Northwest Territories are bordered by Nunavut to the east,
        the provinces of Saskatchewan, Alberta, and British Columbia
        to the south, and Yukon to the west. In the north the territories
        extend far above the Arctic Circle to incorporate numerous islands,
        the largest of which are Banks and Prince Patrick; several islands
        also are divided between the territories and Nunavut, notably Victoria
        and Melville. Yellowknife is the capital and largest city. Area: 1,346,106
        square km. Pop. 44,826 (2019 est.).
    </string>

    <string name="ns_disp">
        Nova Scotia is located in easternmost Canada (upper east coast
        of North America), and is one of four Atlantic Provinces. Almost
        completely surrounded by the Atlantic Ocean, Nova Scotia offers
        plenty of coastline to explore, including the World Famous Bay of Fundy.
        Discover Nova Scotia\'s must-see signature attractions including the
        Peggy\'s Cove Lighthouse, the Joggins Fossil Cliffs (a UNESCO World
        Heritage Site), and the scenic Cabot Trail on Cape Breton Island.
        Come enjoy our warm East Coast Hospitality, and sample our fresh Atlantic
        Canada Seafood!
    </string>

    <string name="pei_disp">
       Prince Edward Island is one of eastern Canada\'s maritime provinces,
        off New Brunswick and Nova Scotia in the Gulf of St. Lawrence. The
        large island is marked by red-sand beaches, lighthouses, and fertile
        farmland, and is renowned for seafood like lobster and mussels.
        Charlottetown, the capital, is home to Victorian government buildings &amp;
        the modern Confederation Centre of the Arts, with a theatre and art gallery.
    </string>
</resources>